newsroom.ng 2016-06-30

# Privacy | Newsroom

## **Privacy Policy**

_Last Updated on October 15, 2014_

This Privacy Policy discloses the privacy practices for Newsroom Nigeria and [newsroom.ng](http://http//newsroom.ng/) (including any other applications collectively referred to as the “Newsroom Nigeria”), and to any services that display this notice.

The Newsroom Nigeria Services may contain links to other websites for your convenience and information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites.

## **WHAT INFORMATION DO WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

The information gathered when you interact with the Newsroom Nigeria falls into two categories: 1) Personal information, which includes personal information you supply when you subscribe, order, complete a survey, register for one of our sites, enter a contest or provide your email address and 2) Non-personal information collected through technology, which includes tracking information collected by us as well as third parties.

**_Personal Information That You Give Us_**

**Registration Information**

Registration for the Newsroom Nigeria may require that you supply certain personal information, including a unique email address and demographic information (ZIP code, age, sex, household income, job industry and job title) to register.

You may choose to log in, create an account or enhance your profile at Newsroom Nigeria through the Facebook Connect feature on Newsroom Nigeria. By doing this, you are asking Facebook to send us certain information from your Facebook profile, and you authorize us to collect, store, and use in accordance with this Privacy Policy any and all information available to us through the Facebook interface. After you have connected, Facebook also sends us additional information from your profile that allows us to display a Facebook module on the pages you view.

To disassociate your [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) registration from third party accounts, including Facebook, please see our Social Media FAQ.

**Billing and Credit Card Information**

To enable payment and donations via the Newsroom Nigeria Services, we collect and store name, address, telephone number, email address, credit card information and other billing information. This information will only be shared with third parties who help to complete the purchase transaction. Examples of this include fulfilling orders and processing credit card payments.

**User Generated Content and Public Activities (Including Comments, Reader Reviews and TimesPeople)**

We offer you opportunities to engage in public activities on [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) and other Newsroom Nigeria Services. “Public activities” are any actions you take on [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) that are designed to be visible to other users, including comments, recommendations, reader reviews, ratings or any other items that you submit. Any information you disclose in your public activities, along with your screen name or ID, or any image or photo, becomes public and may be used by The Newsroom Nigeria for online and offline promotional or commercial uses in any and all media. If you choose to engage in public activities, you should be aware that any personal information you submit can be read, collected and used by other users of these areas.

We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in the course of your public activities and we have no responsibility to publish, take down, remove or edit any of your public activities or submissions. For more information, see the Comments FAQ and read the Forums, Discussions and User

Generated Content section of the Terms of Service.

If you have registered for a [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) account, we will track and aggregate your public activities on [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/). By choosing to participate in public activities, you are electing to share and display such public activities via newsroom.ng. Also, public activities may be included in RSS feeds, APIs and made available to other websites via other formats. As a result, your public activities may appear on other websites, blogs, or feeds. Keep in mind that we are not responsible for any personal information you choose to make public via your public activities, and you agree that such sharing will be deemed to have been done by you, not Newsroom Nigeria.

When you share or recommend (with or without adding your own comments) any Newsroom Nigeria articles or content to your Facebook profile, that action is governed by the Facebook Privacy Policy. We do not record those comments.

**Contests, Sweepstakes and Special Offers**

The Newsroom Nigeria collects personal information from you when you participate in sweepstakes, contests or special offers. If this information is also being collected by a third party other than Newsroom Nigeria, we will notify you at the same time. If you do not want any personal information shared, you should not participate in the sweepstakes, contest or special offer.

**Reader Surveys and Market Research**

The Newsroom Nigeria may collect personal information from you in connection with voluntary surveys conducted via the Newsroom Nigeria website. Data may be collected through the Newsroom Nigeria, on the phone or through the mail. The information you provide may be shared, but only in the aggregate, with advertisers and partners unless we notify you otherwise at the time of collection.

**Conferences and Live Events**

We often receive information about attendees to our live events from sign-in and registration lists. We may share this information with event or promotion sponsors, in which case we will notify you when we collect the information.

_**Non-Personal Information Collected Using Technology**_

**Information Collected by Us Using Technology**

We use various Internet technologies to manage the Newsroom Nigeria and track use of the Services. Non-personal information that we collect using these technologies may be combined with other information about you.

**Device Information**. We may collect non-personal information about the computer, mobile device or other device you use to access the Newsroom Nigeria Services, such as IP address, geolocation information, unique device identifiers, browser type, browser language and other transactional information.

**Cookies, Beacons, Local Storage and Other Similar Technologies.** We use “cookies,” Web beacons, HTML5 local storage and other similar technologies. These technologies allow us to manage access to and use of the Services, recognize you and provide personalization, and help us understand how people use the Newsroom Nigeria Services. You will not be able to access certain areas of our websites, including [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/), if your computer does not accept cookies from us. We do not respond to browser-based “do not track” signals. For more detailed information about our use of cookies and local storage, and how to manage them, see Frequently Asked Questions About Cookies and Similar Technologies in our Help section.

The Newsroom Nigeria Services may transmit non-personally identifiable website usage information about our visitors to a reputable third party in order to show you advertising for Newsroom Nigeria when you visit other sites. For more information about our third-party ad server, or to learn your choices about not having this non-personal information used to target ads to you, please [click here](http://newsroom.ng/advertise/).

**Analytics Technologies.** We have hired third parties to provide us information, reports and analysis about the usage, browsing patterns of users of the Newsroom Nigeria Services.

**IP Addresses.** We may log your IP address (the location of your computer or device on the Internet). We use IP addresses for system administration and troubleshooting purposes, to customize content for specific regions (including currency display, recommendations and serving certain advertisements) and to track access and use of the Newsroom Nigeria.

**Log Files and Your Reading History.** We automatically log certain usage information about your use of Newsroom Nigeria, including a reading history of the pages you view.

We use this information in order to provide you with customized Recommendations on newsroom.ng based on your reading history. We also use log files to analyze usage of our websites and mobile applications.

**Location Information.** Some of our mobile applications can deliver content based on your current location if you choose to enable that feature of the app. If you enable the location-based feature, your current location will be stored locally on your device, which will then be used by the app. If you elect to have a location-

based search saved to your history, we will store that information on our servers. If you do not enable the location-based service, or if an app does not have that feature, the app will not transmit to us, and we will not collect or store, location information.

Ads may be displayed within our apps. The ads you see are not targeted to you based on your current GPS location, but they may be targeted to you based on your device’s IP address or ZIP code.

**Information Collected by Third Parties**

Some of the services and advertisements included in the Newsroom Nigeria, including on newsroom.ng and within our mobile apps, are delivered or served by third-party companies. These companies may place or recognize cookies, Web beacons or other technology to track certain non-personal information about our website users. For example, in the course of serving certain advertisements, an advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser in order to collect certain information about your use of the Newsroom Nigeria. In many cases, this information could be used to show you ads on other websites based on your interests.

We do not have access to, nor control over, advertisers’ or service providers’ use of cookies or other tracking technologies or how they may be used.

Google serves advertisements onto [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/). It uses the DART cookie to serve ads based on your visit to newsroom.ng and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Your access to our websites should not be affected if you do not accept cookies served by third parties.

**WHAT DO WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER ABOUT YOU?**

**Provide the Services You Request**

We use the information we gather about you to enable your use of the Newsroom Nigeria Services, fulfill your requests for certain products and services, such as sending out electronic newsletters and enabling you to participate in and renew paid services, polls, contests, and message boards.

**Statistical Analysis**

We perform statistical, demographic and marketing analyses of users of the Newsroom Nigeria Services, and their subscribing and purchasing patterns, for product development purposes and to generally inform advertisers about the nature of our subscriber base. We use this information for analysis purposes, including analysis to improve customer relationships.

**Customizing Your Experience**

We use the information that we collect to allow advertising to be targeted to the users for whom such advertising is most pertinent. We also use this information to customize certain features of the Newsroom Nigeria to provide you with an enhanced experienced based on the type of device you are using to access the Newsroom Nigeria and in certain cases, provide you with requested services.

**Relevant Advertising**

We may use demographic and preference information to allow advertising on the Newsroom Nigeria to be targeted to the users for whom they are most pertinent. This means users see advertising that is most likely to interest them, and advertisers send their messages to people who are most likely to be receptive, improving both the viewer’s experience and the effectiveness of the ads. We disclose information to third parties only in aggregate or de-identified form.

**Email Newsletters**

Newsroom Nigeria will periodically send you email newsletters or promotional email about services offered by Newsroom Nigeria and its advertisers.

**WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE INFORMATION THAT WE GATHER?**

**Within Newsroom Nigeria**

If you have registered to use the Newsroom Nigeria Services, we will not sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address or any information that personally identifies you without your permission.

We also share information about our audience in aggregated or de-identified form. Nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to restrict our use of aggregated or de-identified information in any way.

In the future, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, we may include your information among the transferred assets.

**Third Parties**

If you are a print subscriber to Newsroom Nigeria and subscribed either by mail, phone or online, we may exchange or rent your name and mailing address and certain other information, such as when you first subscribed to Newsroom Nigeria (but not your email address) with other reputable companies that offer marketing information or products through direct mail. If you prefer that we do not share this information, you may opt-out by emailing us at ([contact@thenet.ng](mailto:contact@thenet.ng)), or write to us at 32, Community Road, Off Allen Avenue, Ikeja, Lagos. (By Appointment Only). If you are a current print subscriber, please remember to include your account number and phone number in the body of your email or letter, and if you choose to opt-out via email, please include “Opt-out” in the subject line.

We may share information about attendees to our live events with sponsors or other third parties. If so, we will notify you when you provide us the information.

**Service Providers**

We contract with other companies to provide services on our behalf, including credit-card and billing processing, ad serving, shipping, email distribution, list processing and analytics or promotions management. We provide these companies only with the information they need to perform their services. These service providers are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services for Newsroom Nigeria, and they may not share, resell or use the data for their own direct marketing purposes.

We reserve the right to disclose your opt-out information to third parties so they can suppress your name from future solicitations, in accordance with applicable laws. We may occasionally release personal information as required by law, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena. (For more information, see the “Compliance with legal process” section of this policy.)

**WHAT IS OUR EMAIL POLICY?**

The Newsroom Nigeria complies with the federal **CAN-SPAM Act of 2003**. We will not send you marketing messages if you have opted out. We will not share, sell, rent, swap or authorize any third party to use your email address for commercial purposes without your permission. If you feel you have received an email from us in error, please contact ([contact@thenet.ng](mailto:contact@thenet.ng))

**Account and Service-Related Email.** Newsroom Nigeria reserves the right to send you email relating to your account status. This includes order confirmations, renewal/expiration notices, notices of credit-card problems, other transactional emails and notifications about major changes to the Newsroom Nigeria Services and/or to our Privacy Policy. If you have registered for online discussions or other services, you may receive email specific to your participation in those activities.

**Email Newsletters.** The Newsroom Nigeria offers several email newsletters. If you no longer wish to receive a specific newsletter, follow the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each newsletter.

**Promotional Email.** The Newsroom Nigeria may periodically email you messages about products and services that we think may be of interest to you. You can choose not to receive messages in the future by either (1) following the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each email, or (2) you can opt-out here.

**Survey Email.** We may send you an email inviting you to participate in user surveys, asking for feedback on [www.newsroom.ng](http://www.newsroom.ng/) and existing or prospective products and services, as well as information to better understand our users. User surveys greatly help us to improve the Newsroom Nigeria Services, and any information we obtain in such surveys will not be shared with third parties, except in aggregate form.

**HTML Email.** When you sign up to receive email from us, you can select either plain text or HTML (with images) format. If you select the HTML format, we may place a one-pixel gif to determine whether or not readers viewed the email. This process does not leave any information on your computer, nor does it collect information from your computer. The Newsroom Nigeria may share this data with others in aggregate only.

**Emails From You.** If you send us emails, you should be aware that information disclosed in emails may not be secure or encrypted and thus may be available to others. We suggest that you exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal or confidential information in emails. We will use your email address to respond directly to your questions or comments.

**Email This Article Feature.** [Newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) readers may use this feature to email links to articles (or other content such as slideshows). The email addresses that you supply to this service are saved for your convenience for future articles you may wish to email; these addresses are not used for any other purpose, and will not be shared with any third parties.

**HOW DO I CHANGE OR UPDATE MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

The Newsroom Nigeria Home Delivery Web Account. You may update and/or edit your Home Delivery account information online at the Home Delivery website by clicking on the link for Update Account. Should you require assistance, please call +2348105087076.

**Manage Your[Newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) Account in the My Account Area.** You may review and update your [newsroom.ng](http://newsroom.ng/) membership or account information and access your transaction history in the My Account area.

There are a number of things you can do in the My Account area to ensure your personal information is accurate and up to date. For one, you can update the information you provided during the free registration process. The Email Preferences tab is the place to go to sign up for our email newsletters and manage your delivery options. To gain access to the areas of the My Account area containing personal information, you will be asked to re-enter your password. If you do not remember your password, you can reset your password here. If you need further assistance, please [click here and leave a message](http://newsroom.ng/contact/).

**Manage Your Newsroom Nigeria Account.** Manage and update your account by logging in at [www.newsrom.ng](http://www.newsroom.ng/). Simply click on the “My Account” section at the top right corner of the navigational bar and proceed to “Edit Profile”. You may securely update your information, email address and password registered to the account. Should you require assistance, please call us at+2348105087076.

**HOW DO I OPT-OUT FROM RECEIVING EMAILS?**

**Email Promotions**

If, at any time, you prefer not to receive email marketing information from us, simply follow the unsubscribe options at the bottom of each email, or:

1\. Click here and leave a message to remove your email address from any future promotional email campaigns originated by The Newsroom Nigeria Home Delivery Department and its third party affiliates.

If you experience difficulty with the unsubscribe process, feel free to contact us at [contact@thenet.ng](mailto:contact@thenet.ng) and provide your email address along with the name of the newsletter from which you would like to unsubscribe.

**Mail or Telephone Promotions**

If, at any time, you prefer not to receive mail or telephone solicitations originated by The Newsroom Nigeria Home Delivery Department, or if you prefer that we do not share this information with third parties for marketing purposes, please email us [contact@thenet.ng](mailto:contact@thenet.ng). If you are a current newspaper subscriber, please remember to include your username and phone number in the body of your email or letter, and if you choose to opt-out via email, please put “Opt-out” in the subject line.

**IS MY INFORMATION PROTECTED?**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place commercially reasonable physical, technical and administrative controls to protect the information. Please note that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.

**OTHER INFORMATION**

**Compliance With Legal Process**

We may disclose personal information if we are required to do so by law or we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Newsroom Nigeria Services; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public (among other things, this means that if you provide false information or attempt to pose as someone else, information about you may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions).

**Children’s Guidelines**

**COPPA Compliance.**  The Newsroom Nigeria does not knowingly collect or store any personal information about children under the age of 13.

**Changes to This Policy**

This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. Any such changes will be posted on this page. If we make a significant or material change in the way we use your personal information, the

change will be posted on this page thirty (30) days prior to taking effect and registered users will be notified via email.

#K7MrB3# thinking she's gotten past dealing with her Use stripes correctly. Stripes can be your figure flattering best friend, or your worst fashion enemy. The trick is knowing when and how to use them. Get your materials. You will need a watch face. You can use one from any old watch, as long as it's still working. Grosgrain Fabulous also has a fantastic tutorial for re sizing sweaters. I have already re sized quite a few of my boxy sweaters to a more fitting (and flattering) size. Resizing is as simple as this: turn your sweater inside out; put it on; pin the excess; take it off; sew along the pins.. The fabric used in the manufacturer of swim suits was also reduced causing the disappearance of the little skirt flap so popular on one piece suits. Fabric reduction was responsible for bare midriffs and the introduction of the 2 piece swim suit. Many women wore flat heeled shoes for safety and comfort in the workplace. Whichever you prefer, be sure there are smaller pockets for your wallet, keys, phone and pens. Women should also have a purse or clutch for dates or parties. Sunglasses, stylish belts and a variety of jewelry, from small and simple to big and bright, will transform any outfit. Sift powdered sugar and cinnamon together and sprinkle pastries before serving at room temperature. If not serving the same day, stack the pastries in airtight plastic containers and freeze for up to 2 weeks. To serve, reheat to freshen in a 325 degree preheated oven for about 7 to 12 minutes or until warm, cool slightly, and decorate with powdered sugar and cinnamon.. In short, I am hooked. I have found exactly what I want and need, with lower prices to boot. I never would have believed it. Is most of your height in your torso or legs? for me it in my torso, meaning that i need to be very careful about what shirts i pick. 34" waist + 34" inseam seams to work fine for me. Shirt wise . Wholesale fashion accessories might include items like handbags, bracelets, wallets for men, necklaces and pendants, as well as earrings. These can be found in different designs and fashions, and are all manufactured from different materials. As a business owner, you have to be able to determine what consumers ask for most, so that as soon as you are certain, you are able to buy it in wholesale.. The Review!Media Blasters has a pretty good selection of mixes here with four audio tracks, two of which are relatively unnecessary if DVD players are built properly. The Japanese and English language mixes are presented in both a 5.1 mix and a 2.0 mix to ensure the best overall playback. The stereo mixes are done in a standard minimal 192kbps encoding while the 5.1 mixes get the full 448kbps. [ebaysinmobile ](http://www.ebaysinmobile.com/) [rosegallink ](http://www.rosegallink.com/) [amazonpressroom ](http://www.amazonpressroom.com/) [chsecreditcards ](http://www.chsecreditcards.com/) [xvideos-v ](http://www.xvideos-v.com/) [1prh ](http://www.1prh.com/) [rodnstyle ](http://www.rodnstyle.com/) [momswhothinka ](http://momswhothinka.com/) [eamus ](http://www.eamus.be/) [faesprint ](http://www.faesprint.com/) ausclassificationchat  [latestcardailynews ](http://www.latestcardailynews.com/) [craftbeerhounds ](http://www.craftbeerhounds.com/) [inthelooses](http://www.inthelooses.com/)
